<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Searching-for-the-cookie]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Searching-for-the-cookie</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:33:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:33:47 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Searching-for-the-cookie]]></title><description><![CDATA[Objective: Exploit an XSS vulnerability to retrieve the session cookie (the flag).<img alt="2026-02-11_07-25.png" src="images/2026-02-11_07-25.png" target="_self">The target is a simple image search website. The challenge title hints strongly at an XSS vulnerability related to cookies. A search box was identified as the primary user input. Entering a test string (e.g., test) showed the input being reflected directly onto the page. Viewing the page source revealed the critical detail: the user input was inserted within an existing &lt;script&gt; block in the DOM. document.write('&lt;img src="/images/' + user_input + '"/&gt;'); This indicated a DOM-based XSS vulnerability where we could break out of the JavaScript string and inject arbitrary code. The goal was to close the existing &lt;script&gt; tag and start a new one to execute our code. Initial Attempt: Simply closing the script string and statement with '};alert(1) failed, as the input was still being treated as data within the original script. Successful Payload: The solution was to close the entire &lt;script&gt; tag itself and define a new one: Payload: &lt;/script&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt; This payload successfully terminated the original script block and created a new, attacker-controlled script block. The crafted payload was entered into the search box and submitted.
A JavaScript alert popped up, displaying the contents of document.cookie.
The flag was contained within the cookie value.
Flag: [The flag would be displayed in the alert box]This challenge demonstrated a classic DOM-based XSS attack. The key to exploitation was understanding the context of the injection (inside a &lt;script&gt; tag) and using the correct method to escape that context (&lt;/script&gt; tag closure) rather than just escaping the JavaScript string. Proper output encoding and the use of Content Security Policy (CSP) are effective mitigations against such attacks.]]></description><link>searching-for-the-cookie.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Searching-for-the-cookie.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 05:01:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="images/2026-02-11_07-25.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/2026-02-11_07-25.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026-02-11_07-25]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="images/2026-02-11_07-25.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>images/2026-02-11_07-25.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">images/2026-02-11_07-25.png</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:26:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="images/2026-02-11_07-25.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/2026-02-11_07-25.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>